## Phan Hoang Vy Thao

## **UX/UI** Designer

<sup>66</sup> I have worked as a Front-end Developer for two years before realizing my interest in designing technological products.

Now I am a UX/UI Designer and I really enjoy my work. In the future, I plan to pursue a career as a Product Design Specialist.



Day of birth





phvythao@gmail.com



(+84) 96 995 2523



Address

District 12, Ho Chi Minh City

Portfolio



Behance @vythaor



@vythaor

Languages



English Intermediate

## Education



Industrial University of Ho Chi Minh City

**Bachelor of Computer Science** GPA: 2.8/4

Sep 2013 - May 2017



KEYFRAME Training

Product design course

Dec 2019 - June 2020



## Experience

Oct 2022 - now UX/UI designer Inspired Lab Technology

Jan 2021 - July 2022 UX/UI designer

**Amaris Consulting** 

UX/UI designer consultant

Prudential Vietnam Assurance Private Itd

Oct 2020 - Apr 2022 UX/UI designer Freelancer

Dec 2019 - Sep 2020 UX/UI designer Spring Knowledge Global

Sep 2017 - Dec 2019 Front end developer Spring Knowledge Global Design UX/UI in web, tablet and mobile for internal products.

Work closely with the Business Analytist team to propose mockup and final design solutions.

Support the Development team in transferring design and asset files into apps.

Identify and improve user experience issues. Find UI problems in UAT applications.

UX/UI design consultant at Prudential

Design UX/UI in web, tablet and mobile for internal products.

Work closely with the Business Analytist team to propose mockup and final design solutions.

Support the Development team in transferring design and asset files into apps.

Identify and improve user experience issues. Find UI problems in UAT applications.

Manage large design files and ensuring that all screens match design system of Prudential.

Bring creative design ideas to products.

Join an e-commerce startup as a designer.

Create graphics, apps, and websites design for products.

Work as a designer in a freelancer team.

Make sketches from business requirements.

Use Figma to create web and mobile projects.

Review visual design and following Design System such as Material Design, Ant Design to create design versions.

Discuss with the Development team and receiving feedbacks to improve the designs.

Participate in Ideathon events to generate idea for new internal products.

Implement websites using Javascript framework such as ReactJs and VueJs.

Guarantee, maintain and fix product bugs.

Using Express, Loopback NodeJs to maintain and expand server source code.